vector.sl 2014-07-04

# Success-Line

### Privacy policy

Company SL Management of Investments (further referred to as Company) takes care of information which concerns our site users. In this privacy policy document (further referred to as Policy) some of the measures are explained, which Company takes for our site users’ private life defense.  
Use of this site means unquestioning users’ agreement with this policy and with all of the terms of his/her personal information processing indicated here.  
In case of disagreement with these terms, user has to abstain from using this site.

1. Privacy of personal information.  
By "information of personal character" here is meant any information that can be used for person’s identification.

1.1. Getting of information of personal character.  
Company gets information of personal character from you, also including that information which you provide at filling of Questionnaires or send us in the form of letters or when you indicate your personal data for money transfer.

1.2. Personal information use.  
We use information of personal character got by registration forms of our site also for registration of users, their identification, for support of functioning and development of our site. It is also used for tracking statistics of the site use and for purposes, which are permitted by you.  
Information of personal character may be used by the Company as well for keeping of connection with the users and also in other ways.

1.3. Revealing of personal information.  
The Company interacts with other companies that provide under our instruction such services as processing and delivery of information, placement of information on our site, delivery of goods and services, provided by the Company also via our site, doing of statistical analysis. For the realization of possibility to provide these services by such companies we can transmit information of personal character to them. But we can transmit only that information which is necessary for providing the services. Such companies are obliged to observe privacy of transmitted information, it is forbidden to them to use this information for other purposes. Employees, subcontractors and go-betweens who have access to this information are also obliged to observe information’s privacy. In case of nonobservance of these obligations they can be brought to responsibility up to termination of their contracts and criminal prosecution.  
The Company can use or reveal your personal data in other cases, including those when we consider that this is necessary for observance of legislation requirements or for judicial decision, for defense of rights or possessions of other users and the Company itself, defense of personal safety of our site users or representatives of the society, guarantee of Partnership agreement or other agreements observance; also for the purpose of investigation or measures taking regarding illegal actions or actions presumed to be illegal, due to corporate bargains such as consolidation, merging, selling of active assets or for other purposes in accordance with your agreement.  
Company can reveal the contents of messages or letters, however we won’t place or issue information of personal character except those cases, described in this privacy policy. Such information won’t be present to third parties without your permission.  
The Company is obliged not to sell or present the e-lists of the users to third parties for other commercial purposes.

2. Our practice regarding information of nonpersonal character.  
The company can collect information of nonpersonal character including information of your visits of the site, about webpages read by you, links which you choose and also other actions regarding your use of our site. More than that we can also collect standard information of a definite kind, which your browser send to any site, visited by you, such as your IP-address, browser type and the language and also time spent on the site. We can use Internet addresses for the purpose of system administration, for control of observance of rightful site use and for identification of site users when in our opinion it’s necessary for interests’ and line of the Company site or other users’ protection.

3. Aggregated information (synthetic data kept in the system)  
The Company has a right to combine in unidentifiable format provided by you personal information and also personal information provided by other users creating in this way aggregated data, which are analyzed by the Company. The Company does not save connections of aggregated data with information of personal character for which reason such data can not be used for your identification or for contacting you. Instead of real names we use your login during the process of aggregated data creation and analysis. We can also provide anonymous aggregated data to companies with whom we interact for statistical purposes and for the purposes of group tendencies tracking.

4. Changes inserted in this notification of privacy  
The Company retains the right to insert changes or additions into this Privacy policy. We kindly ask you to reread this Policy from time to time with the purpose of familiarization with the ways we use for your personal information defense. In case of substantial changes insertion in the Policy, the Company would put up a notice before this insertion or would send you notification E-mail.

Continuation of the site’s use by you means that you agree with the Privacy policy.
